给我点空间 这下好了
All right, give me room. Here we go.
- 这个游戏叫什么名字？ - 轻型摩托
- What's this game called? - This is Lightcycle.
见鬼！
Damn.
你正变得更加野蛮 萨克
You're getting brutal, Sark.
无谓的残酷成性
Brutal and needlessly sadistic.
谢谢 主控制
Thank you, Master Control.
我们截获了一些军事程序
We have kidnapped some military programs.
我可以安排更多的致命比赛
I can arrange more lethal matches.
- 有兴趣吗？ - 当然
- Interested? - Sure.
我很乐意和他们中的一位比比
I'd love to go up against one of those guys.
从那些会计泡沫程序中中断一个给我
It'd make a nice break from those accounting cream puffs you keep sending me.
- 是什么分支？ - 战略空军指令
- What branch of the service? - Strategic Air Command.
很好！
Nice.
听着 这完全是一场误会
Hey, look. This is all a mistake.
我只是一个复合利息程序
I am just a compound interest program.
我的工作是储蓄和借贷 我无法玩那些电视游戏
I work at a savings and loan. I can't play these video games.
你当然可以 你看上去像一个天生的运动员
Sure you can, pal. You look like a natural athlete if I ever saw one.
谁 我吗？你在开玩笑？
Who, me? Are you kidding?
我正在核算短期国库券利率 我只是出来透口气
I went out to check on T-bill rates, I get out of breath.
你们这样会让我的用户亨德森先生非常生气
Hey, look. You guys are going to make my User, Mr. Henderson, very angry.
- 他可是一个完整分支机构的经理 - 很好 另一个宗教狂热
- He's a full branch manager. - Great. Another religious nut.
我应该说“欢迎 朋友” 但不是在这里 不象这样
I'd say, "Welcome, friend", but not here, not like this.
我不知道自己怎么会到这里的
I don't even know what I am doing here.
你是存在于“用户”系统中的吗？
Do you believe in the Users?
那当然了 如果没有用户 谁写了我？
Yeah, sure. If I don't have a User, then who wrote me?
那就是为什么你会在这里的原因
That's what you're doing here.
主控制程序夺取了我们这些程序
Master Control Program's been snapping up all us programs who believe.
如果你是有用的 他就夺取你所有的功能而变得更强大
If he thinks you're useful, he takes over all your functions so he gets bigger.
如果他不能利用你 就送你到这里来受苦
If he can't use you, he sends you down here to the game grid get your bits blasted.
- 你叫什么名字？ - 克罗姆
- What's your name? - Crom.
我是拉姆
I am Ram.
他们会训练你来玩这个游戏
They will train you for the games, but...
但是… 我希望你能做到
I hope you make it.
别的部门变成什么样了？
Hey, what's been going on in the other sectors?
我已经被关在这200个周期了
I have been stuck here for 200 microcycles.
外面简直是在谋杀
It's murder out there.
没有主控制程序的允许…
You can't even travel around in your own microcircuits...
你无法进入自己的微电路
without permission from Master Control Program.
把我送到这里来玩游戏
I mean, sending me down here to play games.
他认为自己是谁啊？
Who does he calculate he is?
真实世界的同时
好吧 克鲁
Okay, Clu,
今天我们来检查所有右手列的数据
tonight we check everything in the right-hand column.
来吧 来吧 你在哪里？
Come on. Come on. Where are you?
- 你在这里 克鲁？ - 是的 先生
- There you are. Clu? - Yes, sir.
这次我要你仔细找到那些文件 这是首要的
We don't have much time to find that file. This is top priority.
- 我知道 先生 - 这次不是仅仅校正我的银行报表…
- I know, sir. - This isn't correcting my bank statement...
或电话账单… 这次是完全控制
or phone bill problem... this is a must.
- 我明白 - 我写了你
- I understand. - Now, I wrote you.
- 是的 先生 - 我告诉了你关于系统所有的一切
- Yes, sir. - I taught you everything about the system.
- 谢谢 但是… - 没有但是 那是为了用户
- Thank you, but... - No buts. That's for Users.
你是最好的程序
You're the best program that's ever been written.
- 你是顽固无情的 记得吗？ - 让我瞄准他们
- You're dogged and relentless, remember? - Let me at them.
那是精神 让坦克动起来
That's the spirit. Keep that tank rolling.
我会在这里掩护你 快走
I will try to cover you from this end. Go.
你认为我们可以融入这些数据流吗？
You think we can merge with this memory, Bit?
是的
Yes.
弗林说检查这边
Now Flynn is saying to look over in here,
我没有看见我们所要看的
but I don't see what we're looking for.
快点 那些鬼数据就在那里
Come on, you scuzzy data, be in there. Come on.
我们有伙伴了
We have got company.
我不能相信这个
I don't believe this.
- 一个识别器 - 是 是 是 是 是
- A Recognizer. - Yes-yes-yes-yes-yes.
他们太多了！
There's too many.
这是什么？
What is this?
见鬼！
Damn it.
- 快离开 - 是 是 是
- Get out of here. - Yes-yes-yes.
是 是 是
Yes-yes-yes.
又失败了！
Busted again.
那是我最好的程序
God, and that was my best program.
抓到了一个非法程序 自称他的名字叫克鲁
Got a pirate program here. Says his name's Clu.
他想要什么？
What did he pull?
他通过一个被盗密码进入系统
He came into the system with a stolen password.
我们发现他试图进入高级内存
We caught him trying to raid our high-clearance memory.
不！ 我一定是不小心到那里的
No. I must have gotten in there by mistake.
- 谁编写了你？ - 我只是简单…
- Who programmed you? - I was simp...
你有麻烦了 程序
You're in trouble, program.
让自己舒服点吧 谁是你的用户？
Make it easy on yourself. Who's your User?
忘了他吧 强大的主控制先生
Forget it, Mr. High And Mighty Master Control.
你无法让我说的
You aren't making me talk.
当心自己
Suit yourself.
替我找迪林杰
Get me Dillinger.
晚上好 迪林杰先生
Good evening, Mr. Dillinger.
谢谢 皮特 你可以走了
Thank you, Peter. You can go now.
是的 先生
Yes, sir.
要求接通主控制程序 用户代码00-迪林杰 密码：MASTER
你好 迪林杰先生 谢谢尽早回来
没问题 主控制
No problem, Master C.
如果你看了一个电子展览 你就等于看了全部
If you have seen one consumer electronics show, you have seen them all.
怎么啦？
What's up?
那是你的朋友-身体检查 又在折腾了
- 弗林？ - 是的
- Flynn? - Yes.
他仍然在找那些老文件 你没办法处理吗？
He's still looking for that old file. Can't you just appropriate it?
我有 我把它放到他还不知道的内存中
I have. I put it in my memory, which he hasn't located.
- 他有可能找到它 - 恐怕是的
- But he might find it. - I am afraid so.
这次我阻止了他并把他踢了出去 但他变得越来越狡猾
I spotted him this time and kept him out,
它变得越来越麻烦了
but he's getting trickier all the time.
我们应该关闭所有入口…
I think we should shut down all access...
直到我们找到那个弗林 仅为安全起见
until we find that Flynn, just to be safe.
- 你有68.71%的机会是正确的 - 聪明
- There's a 68.71% chance you're right. - Cute.
结束
要求的文件为空… 创程序不可用
要求：主控制释放程序创 JA 307020…
我有优先接入权力7
- 你的接入被暂停 请立即找迪林杰先生 - 见鬼！
艾伦 我能吃些你的爆米花吗？
Hey, Alan. You think I could have some of your popcorn?
是的 当然
Yeah, sure.
- 坐下 - 谢谢
- Sit down. - Thank you.
我们不得不关闭所有第7级用户组
We have had to shut down all Group-7 personnel.
暂时的 为了安全
Just briefly. Security.
有人暂时得到了我们的接入
Someone with that access has been tampering.
你不会认为是我吧！
I hope you don't think it's me.
停机期间我甚至无法平衡我的支票簿
I don't even balance my chequebook on downtime.
- 我的家庭需要它 - 你一定可以理解
- I have an abacus at home for that. - I am sure you understand.
只是几天而已 你正在做的项目是什么？
It will only be a couple of days. What's the project you're working on?
它叫创 实际上它是个安全程序
It's called Tron. It's a security program itself, actually.
它监视我们的系统和别人的联系
It monitors all contacts between our system and other systems.
任何没有预定的 它就关闭它
Finds anything going on that's not scheduled, it shuts it down.
我给你发过备忘
I sent you a memo on it.
主控制程序的一部分？
Part of the Master Control Program?
不是 它是独立运行的 同时也监视主控制程序
No, it will run independently and watchdog the MCP as well.
听上去不错
Sounds good.
我们应该可以在几天内让你恢复工作 但愿吧
We should have you running in a couple of days. I hope.
好吧
Okay.
谢谢
Thanks.
孩子
Oh, boy.
迪林杰先生 我对你非常失望
Mr. Dillinger, I am so very disappointed in you.
对不起
I am sorry.
我不能负担一个独立的程序监视我
I can't afford to have an independent programmer monitoring me.
你知道我要进入多少外部系统？
Do you realize how many outside systems I have gone into?
多少程序我要处理？
How many programs I have appropriated?
快点！
Come on.
几天！
A couple of days.
你好 吉布斯博士
Hi, Dr. Gibbs.
系统纪录 1039 主传送序列限制你的
这里什么都没有
Well, here goes nothing.
是的 有趣有趣 你知道你刚才说了什么？
Yeah, interesting. You hear what you just said?
- “这里什么都没有” - 我是说…
- "Here goes nothing." - Well, what I meant was...
实际上 我们计划要将一些东西变走 然后再变回来
Actually, what we propose to do is to change something into nothing and back again.
你应该说“这里有些东西 这里变成没有东西”
You might just as well have said, "Here goes something, here comes nothing."
- Right. - All right. Let's clear the area.
这是关键时刻
This is the big moment.
那将限制你的理论 U-V扫描电波…
I know. This will narrow your theory that the scanned U-V beam...
应该是单脉冲传播
is superior to single pulse exposure.
30秒内进行激光操作
Laser activity will exist in 30 seconds.
戴上护目镜 离开这个隔间到安全区
Put on your goggles. Leave the bay.
让我们看看我们是否得到了绿光
Let's see if we have got the green light.
- 目标区域隔离了？ - 他们确认安全
- Is the target area shielded? - They verified safety.
20 秒
Twenty seconds.
- 看上去不错 - 让她干吧
- Looks good. - Let her rip.
这正是我们在等待的
This is what we have been waiting for.
10 秒
Ten seconds.
5 秒
Five seconds.
完美！
Perfect.
- 棒极了 - 你好 艾伦
- Beautiful. - Hi, Alan.
分解物体很有趣？
You two having fun disintegrating things?
不是分解 是数字化
Not disintegrating, digitizing.
一束激光拆除分子结构
A laser dismantles the molecular structure of the object,
分子暂时保存在激光束中
and molecules remain suspended in the laser beam.
当电脑计算出模型
Then, when the computer plays out the model,
分子回到原位 瞧？
the molecules fall back into place, and voil?
很棒 它能把我送到夏威夷吗？
Great. Can it send me to Hawaii?
你必须提前30天购买你的程序
Yeah, but you have got to purchase your program 30 days in advance.
楼上怎么样？
How's it going upstairs?
令人灰心 我的创就快成功了…
Frustrating. I had Tron almost ready...
就当迪林杰关闭所有第7级接入时
when Dillinger cut everyone with Group-7 access out of the system.
从他有了那个主控制程序后
Ever since he got that Master Control Program,
系统里的虫子比诱饵商店还多
the system's got more bugs than a bait store.
你犯了些错误
You got to expect some static.
计算机只是机器 它们不会思考
After all, computers are just machines. They can't think.
一些程序很快就要会思考了
Some programs will be thinking soon.
不觉得很宏大吗？
Won't that be grand?
计算机如果会思考 人类就不会思考了
Computers and programs will start thinking, and the people will stop.
我要留下来 去输入些数据 明天见
I am going to stay around, put some data through. See you tomorrow.
再见
Bye.
来吧
Come on.
- 你是说第7级接入组吗？ - 是的
- Did you say Group-7 access? - Yeah.
真是混蛋 我都准备好了
What a hassle. I was all set.
- 他有说为什么吗？ - 关于什么篡改的事情
- Did he say why? - Something about tampering.
篡改？
Tampering?
自从迪林杰解雇了他 弗林一直试图闯入系统
Flynn has been thinking about breaking into the system ever since Dillinger canned him.
而且他有第7级接入权限
And he had Group-7 access.
弗林也有进入你的权限
Flynn had access to you too.
我想去弗林那里
I want to go to Flynn's place.
- 干吗？ - 警告他
- What for? - To warn him.
- 警告什么？ - 迪林杰在注意他
- Of what? - That Dillinger's onto him.
我不知道我为什么要帮助他！
I don't see why I have to do that guy any favors.
我不知道你到底看上他哪点
I don't know what you ever saw in that guy, anyway.
我爱他的头脑
I loved him for his brains.
别把零钱放入计价器 我们需要它们打游戏
Don't put any change in the meter. We're going to need it for the games.
孩子 我好久没来这里了
Boy. I haven't been here in a long time.
伙计 这里
Hey, Bobby, up here.
- 他在哪里？ - 我不知道
- Where is he? - I don't know.
迷失在他的某个游戏中
Somewhere in here, lost in one of his games.
你知道弗林在哪里吗？
Excuse me. Do you know where Flynn is?
知道 就在他的机器边
Yeah, he's over there on his machine.
他正在操纵 又一个纪录
He's really on a roll. One more Reco before he ties.
又一个纪录 他破了世界纪录
Another Reco and he gets the world's record.
他要破纪录了 所有的纪录
He's going for the record. The all-time record coming up.
就是它了 结束了
This is it. It's all over.
弗林这把他自己变成历史的一部分！
Flynn's going to be a part of history, all right.
弗林 你怎么做到的？
Hey, Flynn, how'd you do it?
全靠手腕
It's all in the wrists.
999,000点！
999,000 points.
见到你们真高兴
Hey, good to see you guys.
Nothing classes up the joint like a clean-cut young couple.
我们得谈谈
We got to talk.
在这里听不见你自己 来吧
You can't hear yourself think in here. Come on.
- 来吧 - 我离开一会儿
- Come on. - I will be down in a minute.
严肃科学的世界怎么样了？
How's the world of serious science?
就象在家里一样
Go up ahead. Make yourselves at home.
一直等着
Be right up.
英康曾见过的最好的程序员
The best programmer ENCOM ever saw,
而他正在屋子里玩太空牛仔
and he winds up playing space cowboy in some back room.
让我来说
Okay, let me handle this.
说吧
Go right ahead.
你有没有偷入英康系统？
Have you been sneaking into the ENCOM system?
你从没有很多闲聊
You never were much for small talk, were you?
她是否还是把她的衣服扔得到处都是？没有
She still leave her clothes all over the floor? No.
- 艾伦 - 我的意思是没那么经常
- Alan. - I mean, not that often.
你现在明白为什么他的朋友都只有14岁了
You can see why all his friends are 14 years old.
接触？
Touch?
实际上我有做过一些黑客
I have been doing a little hacking, as a matter of fact.
- 你确实闯入 - 尝试
- You did break in. - Tried to.
我看上去不能很好的连接
I can't seem to quite get the connection with that sucker, though.
如果我有一个直接的终端…
If I had a direct terminal...
弗林 你有没有侵吞？
Flynn, are you embezzling?
侵吞是一个丑陋的词 布拉德利先生
Embezzling is such an ugly word, Mr. Bradley.
实际上 我正在尝试找些证据
No, actually, I am trying to get some solid evidence together.
- 我不明白 - 好吧
- I don't get it. - Okay.
让我们回到三年前
Sherman, set the Way-Back Machine for three years ago.
凯文・弗林
Kevin Flynn,
英康最聪明的年轻软件工程师
one of ENCOM's brightest young software engineers.
他是如此聪明 在晚上他开始工作
He's so bright, he starts going in at night,
建立他自己的私人记忆文档…
sets up his own private memory file...
并开始写一个电视游戏 叫做…
and begins writing a program for video games, invented called...
“太空妄想者”
Space Paranoids.
你写了“太空妄想者”？
You invented Space Paranoids?
“妄想者” “矩阵爆破工” “警察缉捕队” 一系列的
Paranoids, Matrix Blaster, Vice Squad... a whole slew of them.
我离自己的事业就差这一小步
I was this close to starting my own little enterprise.
但是进来了另一个软件工程师
But enter another software engineer;
不是那么年轻聪明的 但是非常非常卑鄙;
not so young, not so bright, but very, very sneaky;
Ed・迪林杰
Ed Dillinger.
一个夜晚 我们的男孩弗林
One night, our boy Flynn,
进入他的终端
he goes to his terminal,
试图读取他的文件
tries to read up his file.
我什么也没读到 那儿一片空白
I get nothing on there. There's a big blank.
好吧 现在我们带你到3个月后
All right, now we take you three months later,
迪林杰发布了英康的5个电视游戏…
Dillinger presents ENCOM with five video games...
都是他开发的
that he's invented.
这人渣甚至没有改名字
The slime didn't even change the names, man.
他得到了大提升
He gets a big, fat promotion.
然后开始了他流星般的升迁至…他现在是什么？
Thus begins his meteoric rise to... what is he now?
- 执行副总裁？ - 高级执行官？
- Executive V.P? - Senior exec?
高级执行官？
Senior exec?
期间 孩子们一个星期投了8百万2角5分
Meanwhile, kids are putting eight million
辅币到幻想者机器中
quarters a week into Paranoid machines.
我没有看见一角钱 除了从这儿榨到的
I don't see a dime, except what I squeeze out of here.
我仍然不理解你为什么要闯入系统
I still don't understand why you want to break into the system.
内存中的某个地方有证据
Because, man, somewhere in one of these memories is the evidence.
如果我能进入的足够远 我可以重组它
If I got in far enough I could reconstruct it.
我的密码 迪林杰的转移指令…
My password, Dillinger's instructions to divert the data...
太晚了 迪林杰已经关闭了第7级组接入权限
It's too late for that. Dillinger's cut off everybody with Group-7 access.
等等 你说什么？
Wait. Wait. What are you saying?
这家伙知道你要什么
The guy knows what you're up to.
太棒了 你在跟我开玩笑？
Great. You're kidding me?
现在什么都不能阻止他
Well, now there is nothing to stop him.
现在只有迪林杰和主控制程序运行一切
It's just Dillinger and the MCP running things from on high now.
如果我的创程序在运行就不会了 那会关了系统
Not if my Tron program was running. That'd shut the system down.
如果你的文件在那里…
You know, if your file was in there...
等等 如果我们可以到那里
Wait a minute. If we can get in there,
我可以伪造一个第6级接入
I can forge us a Group-6 access.
好吧？我们应该跳舞了吗？
Well? Shall we dance?
我有很好的理由关闭第7级接入
I shut down Group-7 for a very good reason.
如果我们的人不能接入他们的程序…
Ed, all I am saying is if our people can't get access to their programs...
你知道这令他们多灰心吗？
Well, you know how frustrating it is when you're working on a piece of research.
我很同情 但主控制程序告诉我
I sympathize, but I have data coming from the Master Control Program...
那里有些不对劲
telling me there's something screwy going on.
那个主控制程序是所有问题的一半！
That MCP, that's half our problem right there.
主控制程序是最有效管理我们工作的方式！
The MCP is the most efficient way of handling what we do.
我不能坐在这里照顾每个用户的请求
I can't sit here and worry about every little User request that comes in.
用户请求是电脑在这里的目的
User requests are what computers are for.
做我们的生意是电脑在这里的目的！
Doing our business is what computers are for.
英康不再是你的车库中发起的生意了
ENCOM isn't the business you started in your garage any more.
我们在30个国家有机构
We're building accounts in 30 different countries, new defense systems.
新的防御系统中最长久的部分
We have one of the most sophisticated pieces of equipment in existence.
这些我都知道
Oh, I know all that.
有时我希望回到自己的车库
Sometimes I wish I were back in that garage.
那可以安排 沃尔特
That can be arranged, Walter.
那是没有理由的
That was uncalled for.
你可以开除艾伦和我 但我们协助创造了它
You can remove men like Alan and me from the system, but we helped create it.
我们的精神会留在每一个我们设计的程序中
And our spirit remains in every program we designed for this computer.
沃尔特 很晚了 我有更好的事情要做…
Walter, it's getting late. I have got better things to do...
不跟你做无谓的讨论
than to have religious discussions with you.
不必再担心英康 现在超出你的掌握了
Don't worry about ENCOM any more. It's out of your hands now.
我不认为我有授权
I don't think I am cleared for this.
- 我当然也没有 - 能站开些吗？
- I am certainly not. - You want to move aside?
给我点小小空间
Give the kid a little room.
这家伙有点象圣诞老人
This guy's a little like Santa Claus.
我自己做的 你要一个吗？
I make these myself. You want one?
他们不应该开除我
They never should have gotten rid of me.
- 现在他是一扇大门了 - 闭嘴
- Now that is a big door. - Shut up.
那是我的错 我设计你想要得太多了
It's my fault. I programmed you to want too much.
我正准备攻击五角大楼
I was planning to hit the Pentagon next week.
五角大楼？
The Pentagon?
那应该不会比任何大公司难
It shouldn't be harder than any other big company.
这是我从人类这里学到的
But now this is what I get for using humans.
等一下 我写了你
Wait a minute. I wrote you.
我比那时聪明了2.45百万倍
I have gotten 2,415 times smarter since then.
你想从五角大楼得到什么？
What do you want with the Pentagon?
和我想从克林姆林宫得到的一样 我对公司很反感
The same thing I want with the Kremlin. I am bored with corporations.
有了这些信息 我可以进入
With the information I can access,
我可以比任何人运行的好900到1200倍
I can run things 900 to 1,200 times better than any human.
如果你认为你超越了我们…
If you think you're superior to us...
你不希望我挖出弗林的文件…
You wouldn't want me to dig up Flynn's file...
并公布在泰晤士报可视终端上吧？
and read it up on a V.D.T. at the Times, would you?
你不敢！
You wouldn't dare.
- 嘿 - 嘿 加班了？
- Hi. - Hi. Working late?
是的
Yeah.
好的 过来
Okay, come here.
我让他用我的终端…
I am going to put him at my terminal.
然后到楼上你的办公室找你
I am going to meet you in your office upstairs.
别睡着了 如果我能启动创
Don't fall asleep. If and when I activate your Tron program,
在迪林杰找到缺口前 你只有几分钟时间
you will only have a few minutes to use it before Dillinger catches the break in security.
只要我们不到顶楼
As long as we stay off the top floor,
迪林杰就不知道我们在这里
Dillinger will never know we have been in here.
祝好运 hot shot
Good luck, hotshot.
- 嗯哼 - 弗林
- Ahem. - Flynn.
跟着你
After you.
把那些有问题的程序清除出系统
Keep those programmers out of the system,
把那些我要的汉语文件给我
and get me that Chinese language file I asked for.
终点位置
End of line.
- 你要支持我？ - 为什么？
- You are going to stick with me? - What for?
你是唯一不需要帮助的 记得吗？
You're the one who never needed help, remember?
我怕黑 所有这些科技也令我害怕了
Come on. I am scared of the dark. All this technology scares me.
这边！
This way.
- 他们什么时候安装了这个？ - 这是我工作的地方
- When did they put this in? - This is where I work.
我在激光目标区有一个直接终端
I have got a direct terminal in the laser target area.
你可以整晚呆在那里
You can stay there all night if you have to.
就象一个男人说的“这里没有问题 只有解决”
Like a man says, "There's no problems, only solutions."
记住 这激光是我的生命
Okay, remember, this laser is my life's work.
不要摔坏任何东西 Huh？
Don't spill anything. Huh?
开心点 甜心
Have fun, sweetheart.
要求：接入级别6
密码 SERIES PS 17
驯鹿小分队
弗林你不应该回来
这是所有人都在讨论的主控制程序
Hey, it's the big Master Control Program everybody's been talking about.
坐在那里 让自己舒服些
Sit right there. Make yourself comfortable.
还记得我们一起玩象棋的时光吗？
Remember the time we used to spend playing chess together?
那对你没有任何好处 弗林 恐怕你…
停下！
Stop. Please.
你知道我不能允许这样
You realize I can't allow this?
如果你无法回答不能解决的问题…你怎么能够统治世界？
How are you going to run the universe if you can't answer a few unsolvable problems?
让我们看看你都有些什么
Come on, big fella, let's see what you have got.
我想看看你是由什么做的
I'd like to go against you and see what you're made of.
难道在你眼里物体不都象图片一样吗？
You don't look a thing like your pictures.
我在警告你 你正在犯一个大错误
I am warning you, you're entering a big error, Flynn.
我要把你放到游戏中
I am going to have to put you on the game grid.
游戏？你想玩游戏？我来给你游戏玩
Games? You want games? I will give you games.
这不会发生 这只是幻想
Oh, man, this isn't happening. It only thinks it's happening.
空出入口 程序
Vacate entry port, program.
我说 移动！
I said, move.
看 如果是关于停车票的事
Look, if this is about those parking tickets,
我可以解释一切
I can explain everything, okay?
准备好所有关于战争游戏的程序
Prepare all programs for war games.
我已经为你找到了一个挑战者 萨克 一个新电路
I have got a little challenge for you, Sark; a new recruit.
这是个难题 想平时一样对付他
It's a tough case, but I want him treated in the usual manner.
为了这个游戏训练他
Train him for the games,
让他期望 然后击败他
let him hope for a while, then blow him away.
明白
You got it.
希望你送来一些勇敢的人
I have been hoping you'd send me somebody with a little bit of guts.
他是什么样的程序？
What kind of program is he?
他不是程序 他是用户
He's not any kind of program, Sark, he's a User.
- 一个用户？ - 是的
- A User? - That's right.
他在现实世界攻击我
He pushed me in the real world.
有人攻击我我就回击 所以我把他带到这里来
Somebody pushes me, I push back. So I brought him down here.
怎么啦？你看上去很不安
What's the matter, Sark? You look nervous.
好的 我只是…
Well, I... I was just...
我不知道 一个用户 我的意思是…
I don't know. A User, I mean...
用户写了我们
Users wrote us.
用户甚至写了你！
A User even wrote you.
没有用户写我 我值上百万人类年
No one User wrote me. I am worth millions of their man-years.
如果…？
What if I can't?
你最好和我一起碰碰运气？
You'd rather take your chances with me?
希望我降低你的能量周期？
Want me to slow down your power cycles for you?
我需要那个！
Wait. I need that.
那就齐心协力训练这个小丑
Then pull yourself together. Get this clown trained.
我要他在这个游戏中玩到死为止 明白
I want him in the games until he dies playing. Acknowledge.
明白 主控制
Acknowledged, Master Control.
结束
End of line.
游戏单元18 这里 程序
Video game unit 18. In here, program.
你叫谁“程序”程序？
Who you calling program, program?
新家伙？
New guy?
有一个离线的自由程序
Another free program off-line.
你认为用户们还在那里吗？
You really think the Users are still there?
他们最好是
They'd better be.
我不想逃出这里后…除了冰冷的电路什么都找不到
I don't want to bust out of here and find nothing but a lot of cold circuits waiting for me.
- 你们是谁？ - 停下
- Who are you guys? - Hold it.
当心那些力场
You want to watch those force fields.
如果不注意的话你极有可能受伤 不用担心那些
You will be having plenty of chances to get hurt. Don't worry about that.
我只是想告诉我的朋友…
Look, just so I can tell my friends...
这是个什么梦
what this dream is about, okay, where am I?
我是谁？
You're a......
你是主控制程序的客人
guest of the Master Control Program.
太棒了
Oh, great.
- 他让你玩电视游戏 - 不费力的
- They're going to make you play video games. - No sweat.
我比任何人都善于玩电视游戏
I play video games better than anybody.
出来！这边
Move out. This way.
你 你来这边
You, you come this way.
这是一个错误 我要见主管
There's been a mistake. I have got to see the guy in charge.
你会的
You will.
指挥程序萨克的军舰正在接近
Command Program Sark's carrier is approaching.
他会解释训练程序
He will explain the training procedures.
大家好
Greetings.
主控制程序选择了你们…
The Master Control Program has chosen you...
来服务你们系统的游戏单元
to serve your system on the game grid.
你们中间那些继续对用户表示忠诚的…
Those of you who continue to profess a belief in the Users...
将会接受标准的不合格处罚
will receive the standard substandard training,
这将导致最终的毁灭
which will result in your eventual elimination.
你们中间那些断绝…
Those of you who renounce...
这种迷信和歇斯底里的信仰的
this superstitious and hysterical belief,
将会成为主控制程序的战斗精英
will be eligible to join the warrior elite...of the MCP.
你们每一位都会受到一张身份碟
You will each receive an identity disk.
你们所需做的或学的…
Everything you do or learn...
都打印在这张碟上
will be imprinted on this disk.
如果你们丢失了或不能完成指令
If you lose your disk or fail to follow commands,
你们将会立即被分解
you will be subject to immediate de-resolution.
这就是全部
That will be all.
开始行动
Move out.
那个家伙是谁？
Hey, who's that guy?
创 他为用户作战
That's Tron. He fights for the Users.
创？
Tron?
- 他很棒 - 瞧这个
- That's pretty good. - Watch this.
如果你想活下去 你最好棒一点
You got to be good if you want to survive.
- 你叫什么？ - 我的名字叫拉姆
- What's your name? - My name's Ram.
拉姆
Hey, Ram,
你以前是干什么的？
what were you, you know, before?
我是一个保险精算程序
I was an actuarial program.
我为一家大保险公司工作
I worked for a big insurance company.
给你些实在的感觉…
Really gives you a great feeling...
帮助规划将来的需要
helping folks plan for their future needs.
如果你把这笔直出当作养老金
Of course, if you think of the payments as an annuity over the years,
开销是很小的
the cost is really quite minimal.
是的 那很好
Yeah, that's great.
保险精算程序 好极了
Actuarial program. Nice.
你自己呢？
How about yourself?
我不记得太多了
Oh, I don't remember too much.
我叫弗林
Name's Flynn.
当然 迷惑 在转变中是很正常的
Sure, a little disorientation, that's normal in transport.
你会记起来的
It will come back to you.
就这样了 好运 弗林
This is it. Good luck, Flynn.
长官 新兵正从…
Sir, conscript being moved from pit cell to ring game.
牢房移送到竞技场
You know... Hey.
你们这些家伙应该客气点
You guys sure are friendly.
等一下
Wait.
让他和自己人作战
Let him fight one of his own kind.
你认为你能除去我？
You think you're going to wipe me out, don't you?
不 我…
No, I...
嘿 我…
Hey. I...
那新来的问了你
The new guy was asking about you.
太糟了 他正在比赛中
It's too bad he's in a match now.
我可能再也见不到他了
I will probably never meet him.
也许 他有些与众不同
You might. There's something different about him.
好吧
Okay.
那是很不错的一击
That was a very fancy shot.
好吧 来个简单点的
Okay, here's an easy one.
完成游戏！
Finish the game.
- 不！ - 杀了他
- No. - Kill him.
不
No.
你会为此而后悔的
You will regret this.
我希望他留在游戏中直到厌恶游戏为止
I want him in the games until he dies playing.
这是轻型赛车的出发点
This is the holding area for the lightcycles.
- 弗林 你做到了 - 等在这
- Hey, Flynn, you made it. - Wait here.
- 你赢了 - 艾伦
- You won. - Alan.
你从哪里听到那个名字的？
Where did you hear that name?
- 那是你的名字 不是吗？ - 我的用户的名字
- That's your name, isn't it? - The name of my User.
你怎么知道的？
How did you know?
我是一个认识艾伦的用户的程序
I am a program from a User that knows Alan.
他因为转换而迷糊了 创
He was disoriented in transport, Tron.
我都记起来了
But I am remembering all kinds of stuff,
就象我的用户要求我追逐主控制程序
like my User wants me to go after the MCP.
我的用户也想那样
My User wants that too.
我知道
I know.
准备传输到轻型摩托单元
Prepare to transport to lightcycle grid.
完成传输
We have transport.
这是蓝色摩托队的蓝色领袖
Blue Leader to Blue Bikes.
把这些家伙包入你们的喷气墙中
Run these guys into your jet walls.
- 明白 蓝色领袖 - 明白 蓝色领袖
- Copy, Blue Leader. - Copy, Blue Leader.
这是金色1号呼叫金色2号和3号
This is Gold-1 to Gold-2 and 3.
分开 让他们一对一
Split up. Take them one-on-one.
当心！
Watch it.
把他带入迷宫
Taking him into the maze.
就是它了 来吧
This is it. Come on.
金色3号呼叫金色2号和1号 我正从这里出去 你们也来吧
Gold-3 to Gold-2 and 1. I am getting out of here now and you guys are invited.
明白
Got it.
- 准备好了？ - 好了
- Ready? - Ready.
就这样 傻瓜
So long, sucker.
恭喜 程序们！
Greetings, programs.
武士正从游戏单元逃跑 这是非法出口
Video game warriors escaping game grid. This is an illegal exit.
你们必须回到游戏单元 这是非法出口
You must return to game grid. Repeat, this is an illegal exit.
- 你们必须回到游戏单元 - 金色2号呼叫金色3号
- You must return to the grid. - Gold-2 to Gold-3.
那些守卫正在接近
Those demons are coming down.
抓住他们！
Get them.
派出所有的游戏坦克到那个单元
Send out every game tank in the grid.
抓住他们！
Get them.
我不应该写那些坦克程序
I should never have written all those tank programs.
目标离看保护区域
Targets leaving protective field.
未打中！
Missed.
所有单位离开游戏竞技场
All units exiting game arena.
目标单位加速了！
Target units accelerating.
追击部队失去一辆坦克 队伍靠紧
Pursuit force minus one tank. Close ranks.
喔 伙计
Oh, man.
在屏幕的另一面
On the other side of the screen,
所有的东西看上去都那么简单
it all looked so easy.
他们一定已经越过我们了
They must have gone right past us.
我们做到了…
We made it...
这么远
this far.
追击部队报告
Pursuit force reporting.
我们失去了逃跑目标的可视联系 等待下一步命令
We lost visual contact with escaped units. Awaiting further orders.
追击部队返回峡谷 那些程序不可能成功的
Get the pursuit forces back into the canyons. Those programs never made it out.
我们必须在他们到达中断信号界面前截住他们
We will have them back in no time, sir, long before the interrupt interface.
我们最好这样 无用的家伙
We'd better, null unit.
我会感到非常幸运 如果主控制程序不杀了我
I will be lucky if the MCP doesn't blast me into a dead zone.
我要抓住他们！
I want those conscripts.
那是什么？你看见了什么？
What is it? What do you see?
当心
Watch it. Watch it.
来吧 你这个小家伙
Come on, you little bugger.
看
Look at that.
我们什么时候可以拜访主控制程序？
When do we pay our visit to the old Master Control?
什么？
What?
我们只有三个人
There's just three of us.
如果你认识什么雇佣军 很好
Well, if you know anybody who's got an army for rent, that's fine,
但我的用户要我揪出那个家伙
but my User told me to go take that sucker out,
否则我就会不去了
or I am never getting out of here.
我们不可能找到主控制程序…
We can't get to the MCP...
除非有我的用户的帮助
without the help of my User.
我必须到那个输入/输出塔
I have to get to that input/output tower,
和他联络
and communicate with him.
向艾伦报到 也许他知道…
Well, good. Check in with Alan. Maybe he knows what's...
那是什么？
What's that?
那… 只是…
That... is just...
我现在就想要的
what I need right now.
太棒了
Oh, it's nice.
难以置信
Incredible.
孩子 你已经忘记了能量的美好感觉…
Boy, you forget how good the power feels...
除非你找到一个纯能量源
until you get to a pure source.
我的朋友们 我的同盟军
My friends, my fellow conscripts, we have scored.
我们已经恢复了！我感觉好多了
I feel so much better.
追击部队报告 没有逃跑单位的迹象
Pursuit force reporting. No sign of escaped units.
进入下一扇区
Moving into next sector.
- 谢谢 - 我能感觉到他
- Thank you. - I can feel it.
感觉到什么？你还好吧？
Feel what? You okay?
艾伦-1
Alan-1.
出发！
Let's move out.
来吧 弗林 别喝了
Come on, Flynn, put a cork in it.
一秒钟！
One second.
射程… 9
Range, 9.
位置… 45 48 度
Mark, 45. 48 degrees.
稳住
Hold it.
稳住 开火！
Hold it. Fire.
拉姆 弗林 听见了吗？
Ram, Flynn, do you read me?
追击部队报告 2个逃跑单位被消灭
Pursuit force reporting. Two escaped units de-rezzed.
不
No.
创逃入下一个扇区
Tron unit heading into next sector.
拉姆？
Ram?
拉姆
Ram.
快点 我们要离开这里
Come on. We got to get out of here.
没有生命迹象 看上去我们消灭他们了
No sign of life. Looks like we got them.
继续追击逃跑的新兵
Continue pursuit of remaining conscript.
明白 向扇区边界前进
Acknowledged. Proceeding towards sector frontier.
我们能做到的 拉姆
We're going to make it, Ram.
我们要替你找个地方休息一下
I just got to find you a place to rest.
在那里停一下 拉姆 看上去不错的地方
Hang in there, Ram. This looks like a good spot.
那些坦克不会到这里来找我们的
Those tanks won't find us here.
好吧
Okay.
我以为这会很简单的
I thought this was supposed to be easy.
发生了什么？
Hey, what's going on?
你看见了吗？
You see this?
你怎么做到的？
You shouldn't be able to do that.
现在来些真正用户的力量
Now for some real User power.
这个看上去还能用
Hey, this looks promising.
这个看上去向老式控制器
This is just like the old arcade grips.
让我们上路吧
Let's get this show on the road.
现在我们启动了
Now we're smoking.
你怎么能偷一个守卫者？
How can you steal a Recognizer?
你没事吧？你看上去不太好
Hey, you okay? You don't look so good.
- 我们要想办法让你好起来 - 过来
- We will get you fixed up. Hang on. - Come here.
我的用户！
Oh, my User.
用户 用户 他们…
Users are Users. They...
你是一个用户？
Are you a User?
弗林
Flynn,
帮助创
help Tron.
拉姆
Ram.
该死的守卫者
Damn Recognizer.
只要直行
Thing just goes straight.
我要到那个I/O塔
I got to get to that l/O tower.
程序Alu 要求2号扇区的补充信息
Program Alu, request additional information for sector two.
准备游戏模拟输送
Prepare hangar for game simulation transport.
所有单位注意 抓紧矩阵代码
Attention all units, lock onto matrix code.
准备数字光束传输
Prepare for digital beam transport.
启动门
Activate hangar doors.
模拟的进展如何？
What's the progress on the simulation?
30 56 99正确
30, 56, 99 are correct.
限制4 和 8失败
Limited four and eight are missing.
别叫 尤里
Don't scream. Yori.
30 56 99正确
30, 56, 99 are correct.
受限的4和8不见了
Limited four and eight are missing.
不 我…
No, I...
创！
Tron.
尤里
Yori.
我知道你已经逃跑了
I knew you'd escape.
他们还没有造出一个可以抓住你的电路来
They haven't built a circuit that could hold you.
听着！我们必须要制定一个计划
Listen. We have to make plans.
我们可以到哪里去？
Where can we go?
这边 快
This way, quickly.
停在那里！
Hold it right there.
- 是？ - 什么意思“是”？
- Yes? - What do you mean, "yes"?
是
Yes.
你只会说那个吗？
Is that all you can say?
不
No.
- 别的什么？ - 是
- Anything else? - Yes.
正和反 嗯？你是一个位
Positive and negative, huh? You're a bit.
是
Yes.
你的程序在哪里？他把你丢了？
Where's your program? Isn't he going to miss you?
- 不 - 我是你的程序
- No. - I am your program.
- 是 - 又多一张嘴要喂了
- Yes. - Another mouth to feed.
是-是-是-是！
Yes-yes-yes-yes-yes.
注意嵌套宏
Watch out for nested macros.
- 那些古怪的人是谁？ - 无用的数据
- Who are these weirdos? - Inoperative data pushers.
控制程序！来吧
Control programs. Come on.
高超的驾驶技术 嗯？
Pretty good driving, huh? Oh.
- 不！ - 谁问你了？
- No. - Who asked you?
不-不-不-不！
No-no-no-no.
这家伙在城里不太好控制
This baby doesn't handle so good in town. No.
- 这是干什么的？ 这个呢？ - 不 不
- What's this do? How about this one? - No. No.
头疼
Here comes a headache.
- 啊 - 不-不-不-不！
- Aah. - No-no-no-no.
- 我们要停下这家伙 - 是
- We got to stop this thing. - Yes.
很高兴你同意！
I am glad you agree.
我很好 没问题
Uh, I am fine. No problem.
这个镇上有很多人
Oh, this town is full of live ones.
这就是创说要去的地方
This is where Tron said he was going.
失败的弗林
Losing Flynn.
我不能相信这个
I don't believe this.
站住！
Halt.
更多守卫
More guards.
他们没有看见我们 我走前面
They don't see us. I will go first.
你还好吗？
Are you all right?
是的 让我们再来一遍
Yeah. Let's do that some more.
我想那个警卫看见我了
I think the guard saw me.
来吧！
Come on.
- 站住 - 杜蒙特
- Halt. - Dumont.
我不能支持暴动 你想要什么？
I can't stand this commotion. What do you want?
我来和我的用户联络
I have come to communicate with my User.
困难的提议… 最困难的提议
Difficult proposition. Difficult proposition at best.
让你们进去会令我被毁灭的
Why, I could be de-rezzed just for letting you in here.
他们讨厌这个塔 他们不是不敢关闭它
They hate this tower. They'd close it down if they dared.
他们留着我只是为了…
They keep me around just in case one of them...
万一要和别的世界联络
wants to deal with the other world once in a while.
杜蒙特
Dumont.
我的用户说…
My User has information that could...
可以让这里恢复成自由系统
could make this a free system again.
不 是真的！
No, really.
你应该有程序连线来使用这个地方
You'd have programs lined up to use this place,
并且没有主控制程序监视
and no MCP looking over your shoulder.
当你和我在这个系统中呆上一样长的时间
When you have been in the system as long as I have,
你会听到很多承诺 安慰
you hear many promises, many reassurances,
- 很多勇敢的计划 - 求求你？
- many brave plans. - Please, Dumont.
警卫们来了
The guards are coming.
他们和守卫者在一起
There they are with the guardian.
好吧 尤里
All right, Yori. All right.
谁是你的用户 程序？
Who is your User, program?
艾伦-1
Alan-1.
他调用我 我可以过去吗？
He calls me. May I pass?
所有可见的…
All that is visible...
都必须超越自己
must grow beyond itself,
到达不可见的领域
and extend into the realm of the invisible.
你可以过去 我的朋友
You may pass, my friend.
塔守卫者在帮他
The tower guardian is helping him.
他想
He thinks.
把逻辑探针拿来
Bring in the logic probe.
加大能量！
More power.
开始了
It's begun.
创 定位询问 确定
Tron, location query. Confirm.
确定 艾伦-1
Confirmed, Alan-1.
我正在你的碟片里生成信息…
I am creating the information on your disk...
那将会清除主控制程序并改变系统
that will erase the MCP and change the system.
你尽力将这个碟片送入主控制程序的心脏
Dedicate yourself to getting the disk into the heart...of the MCP.
界面在它的基地里
This interface is located at its base.
在你成功前我们无法再联络了
We will not be able to communicate again unless you succeed.
去吧！
Go.
这是通往新秩序的钥匙
This is the key to a new order.
这个代码碟意味着自由
This code disk means freedom.
我想他们要闯进来了
I think they're breaking in.
- 谢谢 杜蒙特 - 快点 用户们在等着
- Thank you, Dumont. - Hurry. The Users are waiting.
杜蒙特？
Dumont?
程序在哪里？
Where's the program?
什么程序？
What program?
抓住它！
Take him.
靠近点
Stay close.
如果我能让我们到达扫描输送光束
If I can just get us on the scanning transport beam,
模拟会通过游戏区把我们…
this solar sail simulation will take us across the game sea,
送入中央电脑
out of this domain, back into the central computer.
当心！
Look out.
指挥官 你已经享受到了你所赋予的力量
Commander, you have enjoyed all the power you have been given, haven't you?
我很想知道你在一个计算器里会是什么样子
I wonder how you'd take to working in a pocket calculator.
我们搞定了那个你送来的用户
We did take care of that User you sent us.
无效零 现在你有两个叛逃程序…
Incompetent zero, now you have got two renegade programs...
通过被窃的模拟在系统中到处串
flying all over the system in a stolen simulation.
我会抓住他们的 这只是时间问题
We will get them. It's only a matter of time.
你就要到最后关头了
You have almost reached your decision gate,
我不会给你更多的时间了
and I can't spare you any more time.
结束
End of line.
- 是我 弗林 - 弗林
- It's me... Flynn. - Flynn.
- 恭喜 程序 - 你还活着
- Greetings, program. - You're alive.
勉强 是的 我 呃…
Barely. Yeah, I, uh...
拉姆在哪里？
Where's Ram?
他没挺过来
He didn't make it.
来吧
Come on.
罗拉
Lora.
这是弗林 救我出来的
This is Flynn. The one who busted me out.
罗拉？
Lora?
好的 我该谢谢他
Well, then I owe him some thanks.
那没什么
No, it's, uh, no big deal.
我应该了解轻型赛车 我写了那个程序
I ought to know my way around the Lightcycle. I wrote the program.
- 你写了那个程序？ - 我该对你说实话了
- You wrote the program? - It's time I level with you.
- 我是一个用户 - 你是一个用户？
- I am what you guys call a User. - You're a User?
我在什么地方走错路了
I took a wrong turn somewhere.
如果你是一个用户
If you are a User,
你所做的每一件事都是有计划的 对吗
everything you have done has been according to a plan, right?
想的美
You wish.
你知道那象什么
You guys know what it's like.
你只是做你应该做的 无论那有多疯狂
You keep doing what it looks like you're supposed to, no matter how crazy it seems.
程序就是这样的 是的
That's the way it is for programs, yes.
不愿让你失望 朋友 但多数时候用户也是这样的
Hate to disappoint you, pal, but most of the time, that's the way it is for Users too.
奇怪 奇怪
Stranger and stranger.
哦 你们的船很好看
So, nice-looking ship you got here.
你想怎么处理那个塔守卫者 杜蒙特？
What do you want done with the tower guardian... Dumont?
和其他人关在一起？
Put him with the others?
不 笨蛋 准备提审
No, bit brain, prepare him for inquisition.
我需要点娱乐
I need a little bit of relaxation.
首先 准备好追击战舰
First, rezz up the carrier for pursuit.
还有 不要再思考
One other thing. Don't think any more.
这里我来思考
I do the thinking around here.
这不容易
This isn't going to be easy.
如果那些虫子抓到我们 我们就完了
If those grid bugs get us, we have had it.
够了吗？
Had enough?
你要什么？我很忙
What do you want? I am busy.
忙着死 你这个不可饶恕的老程序
Busy dying, you worn out excuse for an old program.
是的 我很老
Yes, I am old.
老得足够能记起来主控制程序只是一个象棋程序
Old enough to remember the MCP when it was a chess program.
他从小开始也会到小结束
He started small, and he will end small.
很有趣 也许我应该把你留在身边娱乐
Very funny, Dumont. Maybe I should keep you around just to make me laugh.
- 发生了什么？ - 主控制程序能量脉冲
- What's happening? - Power surge in the MCP.
- 我们得离开这条光束 - 我不能
- We have to get off this beam. - I can't.
在7和8纳秒没有其它的交点
There isn't another junction for seven or eight nanoseconds.
- 那有另一条光束！ - 太远了
- There's another beam. - It's too far.
他在制造一个交点
He's creating a junction.
我们成功了？
Did we make it?
是的
Yeah.
为我方欢呼
Hooray for our side.
他分解了吗？
Is he de-rezzing?
没有 但我不知道为什么
No, but I couldn't tell you why not.
我是一体的
I am all in one piece.
我仍和你们在一起
I guess I am still with you.
叫那个拿手提钻的人停下
Tell the guy with the jackhammer to lay off.
- 你怎么做到的？ - 基本定律:
- How'd you do that? - Elementary physics...
一束能量可以被转向
a beam of energy can always be diverted.
我们到了吗 妈咪？
Are we there yet, Mommy?
萨克！
Sark.
- 杜蒙特！ - 尤里
- Dumont. - Yori.
创？
Tron?
创死了
Tron's dead.
- 那是什么？ - 那是一个用户 杜蒙特
- Who's that? - That is a User, Dumont.
他来帮我们
He came here to help us.
创信任他
Tron believed in him.
如果用户们不再帮我们 我们就输了
If the Users can no longer help us, we're lost.
所以 我们删了那个程序…
So, we have erased that program...
不
No.
- 你被分解了 - 不是我 萨克
- You were de-rezzed. - Not me, Sark.
你没什么了不起的 只是一个二进制程序
There's nothing special about you. You're just an ordinary program.
你也是 应该被删除的一分子
So are you, one that should have been erased.
你什么都不是
You're nothing.
把那个程序送到牢房去
Take that program to the holding pit.
请！不要…
Please, don't take...
我会把我们的朋友…
I am taking our friend here...
和另外那些宗教狂送给主控制程序
and some other religious fanatics to Master Control.
当我登陆后
When I disembark,
仍留在这艘船上的一切…
this ship and everything that remains on board...
都会被自动分解
will automatically de-rezz.
永别了
This means you.
继续前进！
Move on.
直接向量分离
Immediate vectors detached.
送我们去主控制程序
Route us to the MCP.
我想摆脱净负载
I want to get rid of this dead weight,
赶上通向游戏主域的传输光束
and catch a transport beam to the game domain.
这些墙… 尤里 有些事发生了
These walls... Yori, something's happening.
你没事吧？
You all right?
我还有能量 萨克不知道
I still have power. Sark doesn't know that.
让我独自呆着 我们失败了
Leave me alone. We have failed.
只有当我们放弃时！来吧 看 这墙！
We're only going to fail if we give up. Come on, look, the wall.
尤里
Yori.
你把我救回来了
You brought me back.
怎么做的？为什么要把我救回来？
How? Why did you bring me back?
我需要你的帮助 来吧！
I need your help. Come on.
操作控制器！
Do something with these controls.
我在操作
I am on it.
主控制程序 整个系统的心脏
The MCP, it's the heart of the whole system.
我感觉到一个存在 平台上有另一个斗士
I feel a presence. Another warrior is on the mesa.
萨克！
Sark.
我们越来越近
We're getting closer.
我不知道你是怎么幸存下来的
I don't know how you survived.
那无关紧要
Slave, it doesn't matter.
准备受死吧
Prepare to terminate.
所有的程序都是有用的
All programs have a desire to be useful.
很快 你们就不需要寻求相互之间…
But in moments, you will no longer seek communication...
或和用户的通讯了
with each other or your superfluous Users.
你们会成为我的一部分 和我完全在一起
You will each be part of me. Together, we will be complete.
你应该加入我 我们在一起会很强大
You should have joined me. We'd have made a great team.
- 你很顽固 - 我也比你厉害
- You're very persistent. - I am also better than you.
萨克？
Sark?
我所有的功能都给你了
All my functions are now yours. Take them.
萨克？
Sark?
看！
Look at that.
你的用户再也不能帮你了 我的小程序
Your User can't help you now, my little program.
我有办法了 驶向那条光束
I got it. Steer us over by the beam.
紧靠着它
Right next to it.
那有什么用？
What good will that do?
我要跳下去
I am going to jump.
那是唯一能帮助创的
It's the only way to help Tron.
别 你会被分解的
Don't. You will be de-rezzed.
别担心
Don't worry.
来吧 出发！
Come on, let's go.
我们成功了！
We did it.
太好了
That's nice.
我们以为你死了
We thought you were dead.
- 弗林在哪里？ - 这难以置信
- Where's Flynn? - It was incredible.
他跳进那条光束扰乱主控制程序…
He threw himself into the beam and distracted the MCP...
足以让你把碟片送进去
just long enough for you to get the disk in.
他救了我们 他真的做到了
He saved us. He really did it.
看那些I/O塔
Video warriors, look at the I/O towers.
所有的塔都启动了
Every tower is lighting up.
优先级别一！
Priority one.
尽量看上去专业些 老板来了
Try to look official. Here comes the boss.
一个小时后来接我
Pick me up in an hour. Thanks.
恭喜 程序
Greetings, programs.